A few days after we finished learning, we were on site for the first real photo shoot for the third term students!
I was so happy about that because it's a costume for third term students, and
happy because it looks like cherry blossoms.
And here the next assignment was announced
We would like you to complete the van.
The next assignment will be for you to dance well with the formation that I will tell you about the bang.
Please work hard for it.
Yes, I will.
Depending on the history of it, we will decide whether or not to make a music video for the third term.
Is that okay?
Yes.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
At the camp, we practiced the short version of the bang in groups.
Next, all 11 of us will make up the full version together.
I was told that we would complete the barn with formations and stuff with the third term students.
I have been given the mission.
I think this is our chance.
I hope we can accomplish this mission by supporting each other and doing our best to accomplish it.
I hope we can accomplish it.
I will do my best so that you will think that we have exceeded your expectations.
Good morning.
Yes, it has been a while, everyone.
It has been a while.
I think we've been working on each of us individually at the camp.
From now on, we'll be working as a group.
I hope we can make the lessons to enhance our teamwork.
What is the first decision you have to make for the 11 members to dance the "Bang"?
We have to decide on the formation for this event.
Today, we will draw lots and everyone will decide.
Let's do our best, one by one, so that everyone can shine no matter where they are.
Okay, I'd like to draw lots now.
Let's draw lots, starting with Ishimori-chan.
Yes, let's draw.
Let's draw.
Dokidoki-doki.
Yes, Mukai-chan.
Let's all see then.
Let's go. Se-ne.
Taran.
Okay, number 2.
Okay, Mukai-chan.
Yes, that means number 1.
Okay, Ishimori-chan.
Yes, yes!
For the 3rd term students, for the first time, they got their own position
The center is Rika Ishimori
Although she had no experience in dance, she struggled in the training camp.
But she seems to be having a hard time as the center.
She said, "Bread is never finished.
I want you to work hard with the same passion no matter where you are.
Let's start today based on this.
Please, sir.
I'm begging you.
I don't want to cause trouble for everyone.
I'm a little preoccupied right now.
I don't know if I can remember the short version before I put the full version in.
We had ABCD at the camp the other day, right?
We'll divide into those teams and have them dance once.
Mukai-chan is amazing.
You weren't at the camp, but you're amazing.
I memorized the videos that were sent to me during the camp.
If there was anything I didn't understand, they would send me a video with explanations, so I was asked to teach them.
I was practicing with the help of everyone.
I felt really sorry that I couldn't participate in the camp even though everyone was talking about working hard, and I also felt really frustrated. I'm really trying to make the most of my frustration.
Riko Endo is one of the front members paired with Ms. Mukai. She is also a dance beginner and was one of the ones who had a hard time at the training camp.
There were times when she was very close to me.
There were times when I cried during the lessons.
but she was there the whole time even though she was crying.
I thought she was very strong.
She's soft and cute, but she's got a core.
I think she is soft and cute, but she has a core and that's wonderful.
I'm really bad at dancing, I can't dance at all.
I was determined to get through the camp.
And finally, the choreography started.
The first part of the choreography went well, thanks to the training camp.
Now, the choreography was in, all the way to the end!
To be honest, I didn't think I could do the whole choreography in two days.
So, I had the impression that you learned the choreography very quickly.
I completed all the choreography in the two days of lessons.
What do the two teachers think of the current situation of the third term students?
But I thought Ishimori-chan's growth since the training camp was amazing.
I think she has a sense of responsibility now that she is the center of the group.
I think Ishimori-chan has grown up a lot.
I was thinking "Wow, why me, I'm so sorry".
Everyone is really practicing hard.
I don't want to waste their feelings.
I want to do my best so that I can give a wonderful performance.
Taniguchi and Murayama, who are both pretty good dancers from the training camp, just happened to join the new media team.
Taniguchi and Murayama, who have been dancing well since the training camp, just happened to join the new media team.
I think that's a good pillar for us.
It was the first time for 11 of us to perform together.
I hope Mr. Takai will feel something when he sees our performance.
But it's more fun than dancing alone.
I used to like to dance alone.
I'm glad to feel like I have a great group of friends.
When we do pair dances with other new members
It's a lot of fun because we can exchange our opinions.
I'm the type of person who is quite comfortable spending time alone.I'm the type of person who is quite comfortable spending time alone.
But when I'm with all the 3rd term students
When I come home from a lesson or a photo shoot
I feel like I'm back to reality at once.
I miss you all so much, and I can't wait to see you again.
I can't wait to see you all again.
It's time to put that to the test.
I wanted to make this part of the Niseki Kanade unison, so I wanted to make it as tight as I could.
If you play it back slowly like this, the roughness will really stand out.
I want to make it so that when I play it back like this, everyone is in perfect unison.
The choreography of the band is only alive when everyone's movements are in perfect unison.
But the unison is still not perfect.
We all have to be in unison.
I hope we can talk about the dances and make the moves more and more consistent.
We are getting better, but I think we can go a little further, so I'd like to see more teamwork.
We want to improve our team strength, but there is something that is definitely lacking.
When I do self-study, I tend to check with two people or do it alone.
I've been doing it alone, and I've been doing it in silence.
I would like to see the whole team try to work together at least once in self-study.
During the self-study sessions, each member practices diligently.
However, there is still a lack of awareness that all members should practice together or as a team.
You just gave 30 minutes to everyone, and I think 30 minutes is enough time to get the two dry choreographers to get all tightened up.
What was the point of hardening? It was a self-practice time in the lesson, it was everyone's time, and we wanted them to harden up.
I think that we should not be satisfied with our work, we should not be satisfied with the level of perfection we have now, we have to keep moving forward, we have to keep moving forward.
If we're not satisfied with the level of perfection we've reached now, we have to keep going higher and higher, or else we'll end up with a boring piece.
I think it would be better to have someone like that to lead the group, although I leave it up to everyone to decide how to do it.
The issue that came to light was the lack of a dance leader.
How should we practice?
It's amazing, isn't it?
I think it would be better to decide who is going to be the one to take that step.
Did you notice anything?
After all, the dancer didn't know how to practice.
So it was me anyway.
So I don't know who's better.
I don't know.
Nice to meet you, third-year students. I'm Sakura or 46!
I'm Sakura, 46!
Welcome to everyone!
There are days when we have a performance and something happens, or someone has a hard time.
I know that you will feel the same way, but we will always be there to pull you up on stage.
Let's go for it! Let's go for it!
Wee!
Subtitles & Subtitles by Keogh